<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Meltemcita</title>
    <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Meltemcita</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://meltemcita.today/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Start here</title>
      <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meltemcita.today/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Intro note Oh shit, Birthday day! Dear Meltem aka Queen Elizabeth,
I have been thinking&amp;hellip;
What would be the best gift to make you online?
After imagining many options, some of them involving sending Mikhail to Turkey just to carry some more candies for you, I decided that I wanted to made something different.
It would be so easy to buy something and send you to your home, but you know&amp;hellip; my second name is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd note</title>
      <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/2nd-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meltemcita.today/post/2nd-note/</guid>
      <description>Small Thinking Sometimes in life, we are not aware of decisions or things that lead us to huge new experiences or changes. Even when meeting people, they only cross our ways and we let them enter, pass and forget. It’s more difficult to build a one-to-one connection that’s stable across time than to meet new people. I think you also as a valuable person, someone who is curious and let that curiosness enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3th note</title>
      <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/3th-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meltemcita.today/post/3th-note/</guid>
      <description>UH UH OH OH MelDem,
You&amp;rsquo;re one of the funniest persons I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. Really. And I have really fun friends here in Perú&amp;hellip; but you&amp;rsquo;re like IDK just take it you mdfkcking Meltem language girl squirrel llama human hybrid.
For example, look at this photo. WTF.
 Fcking art. Your hands, omg. accurate AF.  I like the way you take things bcs life it can be actually a joke (you&amp;rsquo;ll see when you take your mushrooms-lsd trip) that’s the best approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th note</title>
      <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/4th-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meltemcita.today/post/4th-note/</guid>
      <description>Dear Meltem Picasso,
Ok so the fact that you found some field that you want and be able to spend a ton of time doing and improving it’s actually a life-goal accomplished in itself.
Finding some time to create something artsy out of nothing is one of the best human skills someone could have. Art is a channel for something beyond us, it is lovely. I admire and encourage you to keep doing it if that’s what you love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th note</title>
      <link>http://meltemcita.today/post/final/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meltemcita.today/post/final/</guid>
      <description>In Summary Happy birthday Meltem!!!!!!!!
I wish you the best, have fun today and also all the rest of your life :)
I appreciate you and I appreciate your fcking existence.
Sincerely.
Pablocito,
 BONUS! And because you’re a good soul that I enjoy to talk with, in other words, you’re my friend. And because we are in a science based society (ZzzzZzZ) I have to deliver some proofs-of-friendship.
And what says more than an image?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
